[Music]
introducing my new hip thruster bars
I'm very excited to announce my new hip
thruster bars now this is the hip
thruster light bar and this is the hip
thruster bar many of you have seen these
bars being used in Glu lab we've been
testing them out for the last couple of
months and we love them
now many trainers including myself have
realized that using an EZ bar made it
easier to hip thrust because the the
plates weren't out so wide it was easier
to stabilize I wanted to recreate that
with a normal bar without all the
contours of the EZ bar now the light bar
only weighs 15 pounds this was designed
with the home gym user in mind you want
a bar that's lighter that you could put
up against a wall but one that's still
conducive to heavy hip thrusting this
has been tested for a thousand pounds
and I've never seen anyone hip to us
2,000 pounds yet with full range of
motion so you can go as heavy as you
want but at the end of the day you can
just store it up against a wall and
maneuver around very easily a
traditional barbell is 52 inch width
from here to here from collar to collar
this bar is only 3 feet across it's only
36 inches and that's what makes it
easier to hip thrust with the overall
length is 62 inches
and you've got 12 inches of loading
capability on the sleeves and the last
thing I want to mention is this bar is
thick and I do this on purpose so
there's more surface area to spread out
to cushion the load right now let's
discuss the hip thruster bar this is 70
inches long
it weighs 40 pounds the width is 36
inches in the middle here so it's way
easier to stabilize it's been tested for
up to 1200 pounds so you can go as heavy
as you can go and these sleeves are 16
and 1/2 inches long now a standard
barbell only has 15 inches so we have
extra room for extra plates so this is
the bar you're gonna use if you like
going heavy and loading up a ton of
weight now this bar has three grooves
these guys the outer ones for your hands
and the inner one to line up with the
center your body so if you have a pad on
there you can make sure that it's lined
up perfectly now we currently offer free
shipping but we only ship to the 48
continental states in the US the light
bar is $129 free shipping and the hip
thruster bar is $249 with free shipping
so order today and get your thrust on